out there how does it feel well it's
feel very cramped actually Oh next time
we do we have a little bit more space
Thank You jr. you're thinking
maybe next time we can have a full
concert full band and write our friends
to play with us and a huge arena that
would be really great but I gotta say
thank you very much for having us here
tonight we're very thrilled to be able
to be part of this
pops in Breda of FWD and to be able to
play it for you guys to being such a
huge boobs I think you doing the news so
much fun having you on the show whether
it was Baxter you know back in the in
the office just talking just messing
around or again here on air thank you so
much mega super dropping by and of
course our wonderful friend from a
centre aid orphanage and FWD wow what
did I was at what a day and that was
like that was 20 minutes that didn't
even feel like already I was okay we can
see what's cool yeah cuz poison he'll
come to mix
yeah my sister's hang out
forget guys you can visit their website
for more information and if WD com cage
and use the hashtag hashtag get ready to
live fifty pesos every time you request
a song about me is also do i do it now
oh and also ya say that it will be
available in iTunes and Spotify
and so you don't load and you know and
that be at the next week nice but for
now just hear it was request already
stuck in my head there you go gonna be
stuck a minute all we know what do you
beg you to FWD to make to the sisters
and you guys for having us over thank
you very much of course our friends from
all over the radio stations but this is
only place you guys can get it so why
don't you guys invite them yeah let's do
us also on jamming 8.3 Olga trainee 0629
p.m. mmm um for every time you guys
request for it Japan will add another
fifty pesos oh yes yeah and lambert will
belly dance
request request constantly you do know
that let us know by law you have to do
that yeah said that on there that is
nice contractual obligation Leonard
believe that
201 bodies
and of course you can catch us on my
show is happening right now this is
brian and light drive on one a 3.5 k
light ad for me i'll catch you guys in a
few hours at six o'clock Oh
what every white man kheyli and then
i'll wrap things up for us here as well
for the rundown thanking each and
everybody that dropped on by it was so
much fun for Miss Joyce spring I'm gonna
tied it for the rundown and we'll see
you guys next time bye bye